Guide to the Werner Pfeiffer Collection, 1953-2017
Archives and Special Collections Library, Vassar College Libraries
- 8000 PUBLICITY and RECORDS
  - 8002: Catalogues, Announcements and Publications
    - Neville-Sargent Gallery, Chicago – 4 Abstract Painters, 1985 (8002—076)
    - The Silo Gallery, New Milford – Boxed Mythology, 1985 (8002—077)
    - West Cornwall Gallery, 1985 (8002—078)
    - Mattatuck Museum – Matters of the Heart, 1986 (8002—079)
    - Neville-Sargent Gallery – Dimensional Concepts, 1986 (8002—080)
    - Berkshire Museum, Pittsfiled – Dimensional Prints, 1986 (8002—081)
    - Shippee Gallery, New York – Architectural References, 1986 (8002—082)
    - Posner Gallery, Milwaukee – Dimensional Prints, 1986 (8002—083)
    - Neville-Sargent Gallery, Chicago – Paintings, Collages, Constructions, 1987 (8002—084)
    - Shippee Gallery, New York – Color Echoes, 1987 (8002—085)
    - Promenade Gallery, Hartford – Illusions, 1987 (8002—086)
    - Mattatuck Museum – Dreamscapes, 1988 (8002—087)
    - Shippee Gallery, New York – Armory Show, 1988 (8002—088)
    - Bruce Museum, Greenwich – Connecticut Biennal, 1989 (8002—089)
    - Bruce Museum, Greenwich – Fun and Games, 1990 (8002—090)
    - Hotchkiss School Gallery – Dimensional Prints, 1991 (8002—091)
    - Landesgewerbeamt, Stuttgart – Endangered Species, 1992 (8002—092)
    - University of Tübingen – Endangered Species, 1993 (8002—093)
    - Gesamthochschule Kassel – Endangered Species, 1993 (8002—094)
    - University of Göttingen – Endangered Species, 1993 (8002—095)
    - Stiftung Weimarer Klassik, Weimar – Endangered Species, 1993 (8002—096)
    - Skeleftea Gallery, Sweden – Dimensional Prints, 1994 (8002—097)
    - Sächsische Landesbibliothek, Dresden – Endangered Species, 1994 (8002—098)
    - Neville-Sargent Gallery, Chicago – Color Spaces, 1994 (8002—099)
    - Hochschule Leipzig – Endangered Species, 1994 (8002—100)
    - Pratt Galleries – Faculty Show, 1995 (8002—101)
    - Harper Collins Exhibit Space, New York – Book Objects, 1996 (8002—102)
    - Paris, Kent, New York Gallery – Book Objects, 1996 (8002—103)
    - Pratt Galleries – Out of Print, 1996 (8002—104)
    - Pratt Galleries – Faculty Show, 1996 (8002—105)
    - Connecticut Gallery, Marlborough – Seasonal Show, 1996 (8002—106)
    - Pratt Galleries – Faculty Show, 1998 (8002—107)
    - Marisa Del Re Gallery, New York – Found Objects, 1998 (8002—108)
    - Hotchkiss School Gallery – 30 Year Print Retrospective, 1999 (8002—109)
    - Brooklyn Public Library – Artist Books, 2000 (8002—110)
    - Connecticut Commission On the Arts – Working Ideas, 2000 (8002—111)
    - Brooklyn Museum – Artist Books, 2000 (8002—112)
    - Pratt Galleries – Faculty Show, 2000 (8002—113)
    - Badische Landesbibliothek – Artist Books and Book Objects, 2001 (8002—114)
    - Loomis Chaffee School – Book Objects, 2002 (8002—115)
    - Washington Art Association – 50 Years, 2002 (8002—116)
    - McGill University, Montreal – Book Objects and Artist Books, 2003 (8002—117)
    - Brookfield Gallery – Stand and Deliver, 2004 (8002—118)
    - Center for Book Art, Chicago, 2005 (8002—119)
    - Hudson Arts – Waves of Light, 2005 (8002—120)
    - Finn Gallery, Greenwich – Books Transformed, 2006 (8002—121)
    - Center for Book Arts, New York – Black and White, 2007 (8002—122)
    - Smith College Library – Artist Books and Book Objects, 2008 (8002—123)
    - Fisher Center, University of Toronto – Artist Books and Book Objects, 2009 (8002—124)
    - University of Delaware Library – ABC, 2009 (8002—125)
    - University of Pennsylvania Library – Artist Books and Book Objects, 2010 (8002—126)
    - Cornell University Library – Artist Books and Book Objects, 2010 (8002—127)
    - WLB Stuttgart – Buchobjekte, 2010 (8002—128)
    - Princeton University Library – Memory and the Work of Art, 2011 (8002—129)
    - Princeton University – Flier, 2011 (8002—130)
    - City Gallery, University of New Jersey – 911 Memorial Exhibit, 2011 (8002—131)
    - Bard College Library – Book Objekcts, 2012 (8002—132)
    - Vassar College Library and Art Center – Re-Examining Books, 2012 (8002—133)
    - Yale University Art Gallery – Odd Volumes, 2014 (8002—134)
    - Toledo Museum of Art – Drawn, Cut and Layered, 2015 (8002—135)
    - Postcard, 1981 (8002—136)
    - Biennal Columbia – Postcard, 1981 (8002—137)
    - Conn. Gallery, Marlborough – Paintings, Constructions, 1983 (8002—138)
    - Arkus Gallery, Connecticut – New Acquistions, State of Connecticut, 1984 (8002—139)
    - Connecticut Commission on the Arts – Arts 2000, 1987 (8002—140)
    - Connecticut Commission on the Arts – Brochure, 1987 (8002—141)
    - Guild Hall Gallery, East Hampton – Prints of the Eighties, 1990 (8002—142)
    - Chesterwood Estate – Contemporary Sculpture, 1990 (8002—143)
    - Sylvan Cole Gallery, New York – Prints, 1990 (8002—144)
    - Neville-Sargent Gallery, Chicago – Color Spaces, 1990 (8002—145)
    - Galleri Futura, Stockholm – Split Target Paintings, 1991 (8002—146)
    - University of Connecticut Library – Endangered Species, 1992 (8002—147)
    - AAA Gallery, New York – Humor in Prints, 1976 (8002—148)
    - Silvermine Gallery – 11th National Print Exhibit, 1976 (8002—149)
    - WLB Stuttgart – Buchobjekte, 2001 (8002—150)
    - Publications
    - Art Direction Magazine, USA, – Position no. 151, 1962 (8002—151)
    - New York Type Directors Club – Position no. 151, 1962 (8002—152)
    - Graphis Magazine, Switzerland – Pages 424-426, 1963 (8002—153)
    - AIGA Journal, USA – Best Children's Books – Position no. 29, 1964 (8002—154)
    - TypeTalks Magazine, USA – Cover, pages 10, 11, 1964 (8002—155)
    - Pennsylvania Academie of Fine Arts Catalog – Position no. 110, 1965 (8002—156)
    - TypeTalks Magazine, USA – Cover, 1966 (8002—157)
    - Gebrauchsgraphik, Germany – Pages 42-47, 1966 (8002—158)
    - Print Magazine, USA – Page 57, 1966 (8002—159)
    - Graphis Magazine 124, Switzerland – Page 152, 1966 (8002—160)
    - New York Society of Illustrators Catalogue – Pages 2 and 8, 1967 (8002—161)
    - Fairchild Corp. Annual Report – Cover, 1969 (8002—162)
    - SAGA 50 Catalogue – Page 13, position 129, 1969 (8002—163)
    - Biennal Santiago de Chile – with US Entry, 1970 (8002—164)
    - First Biennal of Graphics, Cali, Colombia – Page 167, 1971 (8002—165)
    - Novum – Gebrauchsgraphic, Germany – Pages 52-56, 1972 (8002—166)
    - SUNY Potsdam Print Catalogue – Page 11, 1972 (8002—167)
    - SAGA 51 Catalogue – Page 3, position no. 129, 1973 (8002—168)
    - Gallery National Academy, New York, Brochure – Page 4, 1973 (8002—169)
    - UN Playgroup – Young Artist Catalogue – Page 27, 1973 (8002—170)
    - Barton Catalogue – Cover, pages 8 and 10, 1975 (8002—171)
    - Riksutställningar, Sweden, Tinget I sig – Pages 10-11, 1975 (8002—172)
    - Sporrong, Sweden, Katalog no. 1 – Pages 19-22, 1975 (8002—173)
    - Sporrong, Sweden, Katalog no. 2 – Page 14, 1975 (8002—174)
    - Svensk Dam Tidning – Page 44, 1975 (8002—175)
    - Vecko Journalen – Page 42, 1975 (8002—176)
    - Hänt I Veckan – Page 61, 1975 (8002—177)
    - Östgöta Correspondenten – Page 13, 1975 (8002—178)
    - Print Magazine, USA – Cover, 1976 (8002—179)
    - SAGA 54 Catalogue – Page 83, 1976 (8002—180)
    - SAGA 56 Catalogue – Page 72, 1978 (8002—181)
    - SAGA 57 Catalogue – Page 133, 1979 (8002—182)
    - Litchf. Junior Republic, Open House – Page 6, 1979 (8002—183)
    - Print Review no. 3 – Page 60 (8002—184)
    - Pratt Reports – Page 10 (8002—185)
    - Printmakers at Pratt Brochure – Page 13, 1979 (8002—186)
    - Deutsche Grafik der Gegenwart – Catalogue, 1979 (8002—187)
    - Deutsche Grafik der Gegenwart – Poster, 1979 (8002—188)
    - Boston Printmakers – Catalogue, 1981 (8002—189)
    - Pratt Campus – Page 4 (8002—190)
    - SAGA 59 Catalogue – Page 3, position 91, 1982 (8002—191)
    - New England Paper Catalogue – Page 12, 1982 (8002—192)
    - Prints USA Magazine – Page 67, 1982 (8002—193)
    - Kemper Art Collection, Catalogue, 1982 (8002—194)
    - Print Review no. 17 – Pages 68-69, 1983 (8002—195)
    - Wesleyan College, Macon, Georgia Print catalogue – position 77, 1983 (8002—196)
    - New England Foundation Catalogue – Page 15, 1984 (8002—197)
    - Music Mountain Program, 1984 (8002—198)
    - Color Print USA (8002—199)
    - Bushnell Center Gallery, Hartford – Page 9, 1987 (8002—201)
    - RMIT Gallery, Melbourne, Australia – Catalogue, 1987 (8002—202)
    - Gallery Guide of Chicago – Page 6, 1987 (8002—203)
    - Chesterwood Estate, Contemporary Sculpture – page 15, 1987 (8002—204)
    - Art Today Magazine – Page 42, 1987 (8002—205)
    - Mattatuck Museum Catalogue, Connecticut Vision – position 72, 1989 (8002—206)
    - Connecticut Biennial, Bruce Museum – Page 23, 1989 (8002—207)
    - Chesterwood Estate, Contemporary Sculpture – page 39, 1990 (8002—208)
    - Wellesly Book Art Brochure – Quotes from Liber Mobile, 1992 (8002—209)
    - Der Druckspiegel Magazine – Page 10, 1993 (8002—210)
    - Stiftung Weimarer Klassik – Page 1, 1993 (8002—211)
    - Festival of Trees – X-mas Tree Ornament, 1994 (8002—212)
    - New york Times, Book Section, Bookends, 1996 (8002—213)
    - Exhibition Management Offerings – Page 13, 1997 (8002—214)
    - CBA, New York – Textiles /Fiber /Thread, Exhibition Catalogue, 1999 (8002—215)
    - Hartford Courant, Out of Germany's Past, 1999 (8002—216)
    - Grapheion Magazine – Page 14, 1999 (8002—217)
    - Forum Connecticut – Wonders of Creativity, Stage Debate, 1999 (8002—218)
    - Umbrella Magazine – Page 52, 2000 (8002—219)
    - Prattler Magazine – Page 4-5, 2000 (8002—220)
    - Splendid Pages, Catalogue Toledo Museum – Page 140-141, 2003 (8002—221)
    - Resonance/Response, Exhibit Catalogue – Page 8, 2005 (8002—222)
    - Black and White and Read – CBA, New York, Exhibition Catalogue, 2007 (8002—223)
    - Pratt Folio – Page 10 (8002—224)
    - Yale Art Gallery Bulletin, New Acquisitions – Page 233, 2008 (8002—225)
    - University of Connecticut Library Magazine 2 – Page 3, 2008 (8002—226)
    - University of Connecticut Library Magazine 6 – Front page and page 6, 2008 (8002—227)
    - Beyond Text, Catalogue, Grolier Club, New York – Pages 131-132, 2010 (8002—228)
    - Wellesly Magazine – Page 40, 2010 (8002—229)
    - Visual Arts Gallery, University of Jersey City, 911 Memorial Exhibit – page 16, 2011 (8002—230)
    - The Miscellany News, Vassar – Page 16, 2012 (8002—231)
    - Tongs in Trees, Vassar – Exhibit Catalogue, 2014 (8002—232)
    - Odd Volumes, Yale Art Gallery – Pages 138-139, C 252, 2014 (8002—233)
    - arTMAters, Toledo Museum Magazine – Pages 10-12, 2015 (8002—234)
    - Poughkeepsie Journal – Page E 5, 2015 (8002—235)
    - New York Times, March 19, 2015 – F 18-19 (8002—236)
    - Journal of the Print World – Pages 18-19, 2015 (8002—237)
    - Chronogram Magazine, February 2015 – Cover and page 12 (8002—238)
    - Toledo Blade – Front page and page 5, 2015 (8002—239)
    - Fine BOOKS Magazine, Spring 2015 – Pages 47-49 (8002—240)
    - Shape Shifting, Catalogue, University of Colorado – Page 28, 1999 (8002—241)
    - Artists Book Catalogue, Brooklyn Museum – Position 27, 2000 (8002—242)
    - Stand and Deliver, Exhibition Catalogue – Pages 4-6, 2004 (8002—243)
    - Seductive Alchemy, Texas Woman University – Catalogue pages 122,128 and 129, 2013 (8002—244)
  - 8003: Audio-Visual Material, Exhibits + Certificates, Writing
    - NBC Today Show – Werner Pfeiffer prints, 1976-11-04 (8003—001)
    - Interview on 'Open Air' – Connecticut Public Radio, 1983-06 (8003—002)
    - Interview on 'Open Air' – Connecticut Public Radio, 1986-08-07 (8003—003)
    - Art Talk – Public Access Television, Channel 38, Eastern Connecticut (8003—004)
    - It Began with a Book, Public Access Television, Litchfield County, 1990 (8003—005)
    - Li-Bra-Ry project, Spring 1991 (8003—006)
    - Interview Channel 5 Norwalk, CT, Harriet Hillers World of Art, 1992-10 (8003—007)
    - PBS City Arts – Book Art, 1998-01-29 (8003—008)
    - The Wonders of Creativity, The Conn. Forum, Hartford, Connecticut, 1999-02-06 (8003—009)
    - Buchobjekte – Württembergische Landesbibliothek, 2001-11-22 (8003—010)
    - Exhibitions and Certificates
    - Prints and Exhibition at Hotchkiss, 1999 (8003—011)
    - Exhibition at the Badische Landesbibliothek in Karlsruhe, spring-summer 2001 (8003—012)
    - Württembergische Landesbibliothek, Exhibition, Winter 2001 -Spring 2002 (8003—013)
    - McGill University, Montreal, Exhibition, 2003 (8003—014)
    - Toledo Museum of Art, Drawn, Cut and Layered Exhibition, spring 2015 (8003—015)
    - 20 Certificates and Awards (8003—016)
    - Writing
    - Werner Pfeiffer – written material (8003—017)
    - Bibliography, Internet listings, Papers (8003—018)
    - Research material (8003—019)
    - Manuscript 'Questions,', 2005 (8003—020)
    - Rejections – search for agent (8003—021)
  - 8006: Correspondence and Records
    - AAA Gallery (8006—001)
    - Barton, John (8006—002)
    - Brusberg, Germany (8006—003)
    - Concept Art (8006—004)
    - Connecticut Commission On the Arts (8006—005)
    - Connecticut Gallery (8006—006)
    - Finn Gallery (8006—007)
    - Futura, Sweden (8006—008)
    - Gallery of Graphic Arts (8006—009)
    - Grafikhuset, Stockholm (8006—010)
    - Jellinghouse, Fritz (8006—011)
    - Knauer Expo (8006—012)
    - Letters to Galleries (8006—013)
    - Malten Gallery (8006—014)
    - Mannes Gallery (8006—015)
    - Mattatauck Museum (8006—016)
    - Neville-Sargent Gallery (8006—017)
    - Posner (BGH) Gallery (8006—018)
    - Pratt Adlib Press (8006—019)
    - Pratt, Brooklyn Museum (Keepsake) (8006—020)
    - Salomone (DSA Fine Arts) (8006—021)
    - Selkowitz, Judith (8006—022)
    - Shippee Gallery (8006—023)
    - Silvermine (8006—024)
    - Skelefteå (8006—025)
    - Sporrong (8006—026)
    - Sylvan Cole Gallery (8006—027)
    - Szoke-Koo Gallery (8006—028)
    - Trimper, Isabel (8006—029)
    - Binder with alphabetic correspondence (8006—030)
    - Endangered Species – Berlin (8006—031)
    - Endangered Species – Cantz Book (8006—032)
    - Endangered Species – Dresden (8006—033)
    - Endangered Species – Follow – Up (8006—034)
    - Endangered Species – General Correspondence (8006—035)
    - Endangered Species – Göttingen (8006—036)
    - Endangered Species – Kassel (8006—037)
    - Endangered Species – Leipzig (8006—038)
    - Endangered Species – Li-Bra-Ry (8006—039)
    - Endangered Species – Lund (8006—040)
    - Endangered Species – Mailing Lists (8006—041)
    - Endangered Species – Miscellany (8006—042)
    - Endangered Species – Negative Answers (8006—043)
    - Endangered Species – No Answers (8006—044)
    - Endangered Species – Pictorial Material (8006—045)
    - Endangered Species – Prague (8006—046)
    - Endangered Species – Press Clippings (8006—047)
    - Endangered Species – Stuttgart (8006—048)
    - Endangered Species – Text – Germany (8006—049)
    - Endangered Species – Text – English (8006—050)
    - Endangered Species – Tübingen (8006—051)
    - Endangered Species – University of Connecticut (8006—052)
    - Endangered Species – Weimar (8006—053)
  - # 8007 Publicity and Records — Posters
    - University of Darmstadt, Germany – Lecture, 1972; (20.5 x 16.5) (8007—001)
    - Wallnuts Gallery, Philadelphia – Exhibition, 1971; (16 x 21.5) (8007—002)
    - Galerie Maerklin, Stuttgart – Exhibition, 1974; (19.5 x 28) (8007—003)
    - International Artists Gallery, Miami – Exhibition, 1974; (19.75 x 25.5) (8007—004)
    - Linköpings Stads Museum – Exhibition, 1975; (16 x 26) (8007—005)
    - Galeri Grafikhuset, Stockholm – Exhibition, 1975; (19 x 26) (8007—006)
    - Galerie Brusberg, Hanover – Exhibition, 1976; (18 x 22) (8007—007)
    - Galerie Roger, Nice – Exhibition, 1979; (13 x 31) (8007—008)
    - Galerie der Stadt Stuttgart – Exhibition, 1980; (23.25 x 33) (8007—009)
    - Galerie Brusberg, Hanover – Exhibition, 1980; (12 x 24.5) (8007—010)
    - Neville-Sargent Gallery, Evanston – Exhibition, 1983; (25.75 x 33) (8007—011)
    - Music Mountain, Lakeville – Sculpture Park, 1984; (33 x 25.25) (8007—012)
    - Mattatuck Museum, Waterbury – Exhibition, 1989; (22 x 34.5) (8007—013)
    - Universitätsbibliothek Tübingen – Exhibition, 1993; (16.5 x 23.25) (8007—014)
    - Gesamthochschule Kassel – Exhibition, 1993; (16.5 x 23.25) (8007—015)
    - Nieders. Staatsbibliothek, Göttingen – Exhibition, 1993; (16.5 x 23.25) (8007—016)
    - Stiftung Weimarer Klassik, Weimar – Exhibition, 1993; (16.5 x 23.25) (8007—017)
    - Sächsische Landesbibliothek, Dresden – Exhibition, 1994; (16.5 x 23.25) (8007—018)
    - Hochsch. für Grafik und Buchkunst, Leipzig – Exhibition, 1994; (16.5 x 23.25) (8007—019)
    - Harper-Collins Exhibition Space, New York – Exhibition, 1996; (8.5 x 11) (8007—020)
    - Badische Landesbibliothek, Karlsruhe – Exhibition, 2001; (13 x 25.5) (8007—021)
    - Württemb. Landesbibliothek, Stuttgart – Exhibition, 2001; (16.5 x 23.25) (8007—022)
    - McGill University Library, Montreal – Exhibition, 2003; (10 x 30) (8007—023)
    - Württemb. Landesbibliothek, Stuttgart – Exhibition, 2007; (23.25 x 33) (8007—024)
    - Smith College Library, Northampton – Exhibition, 2008; (16 x 24) (8007—025)
    - Fisher Center, University of Toronto – Exhibition, 2009; (16 x 24) (8007—026)
    - University of Pennsylvania, Philadelphia – Exhibition, 2010; (16 x 24) (8007—027)
    - Cornell University Library, Ithaca – Exhibition, 2010; (10 x 17) (8007—028)
    - Drexel University, Philadelphia – Seminar, Lecture, 2012; (11 x 17) (8007—029)
    - Bucknell University Library – Exhibition, 2016; (17 x 11) (8007—030)
- 9000 PRIVATE COLLECTION ITEMS
  - 9003: Prints
    - Samual Alexander – woodengraving, 1964; (7.75 x 9.5) (9003—001)
    - Richard Bober – intaglio, 1963; (12.5 x 14) (9003—002)
    - Richard Bober – intaglio, 1963; (12.5 x 14) (9003—003)
    - Linda Bruce – woodcut, 1963; (10 x 12 ) (9003—004)
    - Linda Bruce – woodcut, 1963; (10.75 x 6.5) (9003—005)
    - Linda Bruce – intaglio, 1963; (10 x 13) (9003—006)
    - Linda Bruce – intaglio, 1963; (10 x 13) (9003—007)
    - Linda Bruce – intaglio, 1963; (10 x 13) (9003—008)
    - Linda Bruce – intaglio, 1963; (10 x 13) (9003—009)
    - Linda bruce – intaglio, 1963; (10 x 13) (9003—010)
    - Linda Bruce – intaglio, 1963; (10 x 13) (9003—011)
    - Linda Bruce – intaglio, 1963; (10 x 13) (9003—012)
    - Linda bruce – intaglio, 1963; (10 x 13) (9003—013)
    - Fritz Eichenberg – 12 woodengravings, 1977; (9 x 12) (9003—014)
    - Fritz Eichenberg – woodengraving, unsigned, 1978; (17 x 14) (9003—015)
    - Fritz Eichenberg – woodengraving on poster, 1968; (18 x 26) (9003—016)
    - Fritz Eichenberg – woodengraving, 1976; (18 x 26) (9003—017)
    - Theresa Fehrman – intaglio, 1961; (7.5 x 11.75) (9003—018)
    - Theresa Fehrman – intaglio, 1962; (13.75 x 10.75) (9003—019)
    - Wolfgang Gaefken – woodcut, unsigned, 1959; (12 x 17) (9003—020)
    - Hans Gekeler – offset print, 4 sections, 1982; (11.75 x 11.75) (9003—021)
    - Hans Gekeler – silkscreen, 1977; (10 x 10) (9003—022)
    - James Grashow – 9 woodengravings, 1962; (9.5 x 12.5) (9003—023)
    - James Grashow – woodengraving, 1967; (11.5 x 15.5) (9003—024)
    - Debrah Joyce – intaglio, 1963; (10.5 x 11.5) (9003—025)
    - Debrah Joyce – intaglio, 1963; (11.5 x 10.5) (9003—026)
    - Know Martin – color intaglio, 1965; (8 x 10) (9003—027)
    - Jacob Landau – woodcut, 1968; (12 x 17) (9003—028)
    - Jacob Landau – woodcut, 1968; (12 x 17) (9003—029)
    - Jacob Landau – offset lithography, 1967; (8.5 x 11) (9003—030)
    - Jacob Landau – offset lithography, 1967; (11 x 17) (9003—031)
    - Ilse Nesbit – woodcut, 2006; (11 x 15 ) (9003—032)
    - Michael Ponce de Leon – intaglio, 1974; (6 x 6.5) (9003—033)
    - Michael Ponce de Leon – collage intaglio, 1975; (17 x 12) (9003—034)
    - Michael Ponce de Leon – collage intaglio, 1976; (23 x 4.5) (9003—035)
    - Anthony Saris – linocut, 1969; (12 x 8.5) (9003—036)
    - Kanako Tanabe – woodcut, 1961; (12 x 16.5) (9003—037)
    - Vasilious Toulis – silkscreen, 1966; (13.5 x 16) (9003—038)
    - Vasilious Toulis – intaglio, 1963; (13.5 x 19.25 (9003—039)
    - Carole Uehara – color intaglio, 1964; (13.25 x 14) (9003—040)
    - Carole Uehara – color intaglio, 1964; (13.25 x 14) (9003—041)
    - Carole Uehara – color intaglio, 1964; (13.25 x 14) (9003—042)
    - Carole Uehara – color intaglio, 1964; (13.25 x 14) (9003—043)
  - 9004: Greeting Cards
    - Eric Carle — 12 signed and numbered prints, (8 x 10) (9004—001)
    - Fritz Eichenberg — 10 signed x-mas prints (9004—002)
    - Hans Gekeler — 15 handpainted and collaged cards (9004—003)
    - Kumi Korf — 6 original handmade cards (9004—004)
    - Hedi Kyle — 10 handmade seasons greeting cards (9004—005)
    - Claire Romano and John Ross — 12 seasons greeting prints (9004—006)
    - 6 cards by various artists (9004—007)
  - 9005: Pratt Adlib Press
    - Adlib No. 1 (incomplete), 1953; (11 x 13) (9005—001)
    - Adlib No. 2, 1954; (9 x 12) (9005—002)
    - Adlib No. 3, 1955; (12.5 x 9) (9005—003)
    - Ablib No. 4, 1956; (8.5 x 11.75) (9005—004)
    - Ablib No. 5, 1957; (9 x 11.75) (9005—005)
    - Adlib No. 6 (incomplete), 1958; (10.5 x 13) (9005—006)
    - Adlib No. 7, 1959; (9.75 x 10.5) (9005—007)
    - Adlib No. 8, 1960; (9 x 12) (9005—008)
    - Adlib No. 9, 1961; (9 x 12) (9005—009)
    - Adlib No. 10, 1962; (9 x 12) (9005—010)
    - Adlib No. 11, 1963; (9 x 12) (9005—011)
    - Adlib No. 12, 1964; (9 x 12) (9005—012)
    - Adlib No. 13, 1965; (9 x 12) (9005—013)
    - Adlib No. 14, 1966; (9 x 12) (9005—014)
    - Adlib No. 15, 1967; (9 x 12) (9005—015)
    - Adlib No. 16, 1968; (9 x 12) (9005—016)
    - A Profile of Marianne Moore – Keepsake no. 2, 1960; (9 x 12) (9005—017)
    - Munakata – The Way of the Woodcut – Keepsake no. 3, 1961; (8 x 12) (9005—018)
    - The Pterodactyl and the Lamb, 1962; (5 x 7) (9005—019)
    - Exiles – Keepsake no. 4, 1962; (9 x 8.5) (9005—020)
    - The Imaged Word – Keepsake no. 5, 1962; (6.75 x 9.25) (9005—021)
    - Time and the Machine – Keepsake no. 6, 1963; (6 x 9.75 ) (9005—022)
    - Auto-Images – Keepsake no. 7, 1964; (6 x 11) (9005—023)
    - A Frasconi FamilyTravelogue, 1964; (8.5 x 11) (9005—024)
    - Etienne Decroux: Art of the Mime – Keepsake no. 8, 1965; (10.5 x 14.5) (9005—025)
    - A princess of Mars – Keepsake no. 9, 1965; (10 x 12.5) (9005—026)
    - Dr. Jekyll and mr. Hyde – Keepsake no. 12, 1967; (8.75 x 11.25) (9005—027)
    - Wood Type Calendar – Keepsake no. 13, 1968; (8.25 x 8) (9005—028)
    - The Possible Theater, 1966; (11.25 x 17) (9005—029)
    - Square Variables – Keepsake no. 14, 1972; (16 x 16) (9005—030)
    - The How to Fool Mother Nature Guide – Keepsake no. 15, 1973; (13 x 17.25) (9005—031)